### **CURRICULUM VITAE (RESUME)**

# LILIAN KERUBO MOTOKI OFFICE ADMINISTARTION/CUSTOMERCARE/TEAM RECEPTIONIST/TEAM LEADER

P.O. Box 16702-20100, Nakuru Phone: 0722740184,0706570192; E-mail: nyandusililian8@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I am interested in pursuing a new work opportunity in which I will be able to utilize my experience in office administration, team leader and customer care services. Am interested in administrative and customer service roles; providing executive support, communication, organizing and supervising a team and information flow management, handling and guiding customers. My strengths are in anticipating, actively pursuing and providing innovative administrative solutions while upholding integrity and a strong work ethic which ensure continual value-add to any team I am a part of.

#### **EDUCATIONAL & PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS**

- 2015: PARAMILITARY TRAINING & NATION BUILDING. (NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE COLLEGE) (N.Y.S)
- **2014**: CERTIFICATE IN COMPUTER APPLICATIONS.(*AMAZON COMPUTER COLLEGE*).
- 2013: KENYA CERTIFICATE OF SECONDARY EDUCATION (KCSE). (ST.GABRIEL MISSION SECONDARY SCHOOL)HIGH SCHOOL
- 2009: KENYA CERTIFICATE OF PRIMARY EDUCATION (MILIMANI ACADEMY)

#### **CORE SKILLS & COMPETENCIES**

Administration/Customer service/ Secretarial support/Diary and Calendar Management/Logistics/Front Office and Reception Management/Information flow Management/Customer Service/Petty Cash Management/Records Management/Good Communication and interpersonal Skills/Microsoft Word and Excel

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **JULY 2021 - FEBRUARY 2024:**

## OFFICE ADMINISTRATOR TEAM LEADER TOMBE & COMPANY ADVOCATES

#### My duties included:-

- Received and sorted necessary correspondences
- Trained receptionist and employees and prepared them for their roles.
- Recorded and managed office expenses
- Assigning day to day court duties to the team
- Supervising assigned work to the team
- In cases of any problem, I created solutions in absence of the manager
- Coming up with strategies to ensure work efficiency and flow
- Handling of incoming and outgoing mails
- Process and maintain records for safety, ease of reference, retrieval and issue
- Perform any other duties that may be assigned from time to time by the manager
- Handling of incoming and outgoing calls

- Typesetting
- Photocopying, scanning and responding to e-mails
- Attending to clients and responding to queries.
- Diarizing office diaries.
- Receiving, guiding and directing visitors.
- Train and evaluate old & new staffs
- Booking appointments.
- Preparing of court proceedings
- Customer handling.

### JUNE 2018 - JULY 2021: <u>RECEPTIONIST/FRONT OFFICE AND GENERAL</u> <u>OFFICE ADMINISTRATION</u>

#### My key duties included:-

- Attending to clients at the reception
- Customer services
- Booking appointments
- Calling clients and updating them of their cases
- Ensuring a conducive office environment with regard to cleanliness, availability of working equipment, stationery etc
- Dealing with correspondences including drafting and responding to routine correspondence as necessary
- Handling of incoming and outgoing calls
- Receiving court documents and filing them in their respective files.
- Filing of documents in their respective files and folders.

#### General Administration duties included:

- Typing letters, minutes and other correspondences.
- Scanning, photocopying and emailing documents

### JANUARY 2016 –APRIL2018: <u>CUSTOMER SERVICE/SALES PERSON AT</u> <u>GLOVINE MOTORS BAZAARS LIMITED</u>

#### My key duties included:-

- General customer handling duties
- Welcoming customers and visitors
- Handling of incoming and outgoing calls
- Performed online marketing of motor vehicles.
- Keeping records.
- Calling clients and making sure they are up to date with their payments.
- I also did sales and marketing of motor vehicle in the showroom.
- Maintaining effective filing system for storage and retrieval information.

#### PERSONAL INTERESTS & AFFILIATIONS

**Personal interests**: Networking, Travelling and swimming. **Affliations**: Member of the Family care and Youth Counseling.

#### **REFEREES**

GEORGE RASUGU ADVOCATE MBOGA GG & COMPANY ADVOCATES P.O BOX 14594-20100

**NAKURU** 

Tel: 0707699595

Email: ggmbogacoadvocates@gmail.com

MADAM PATRICIA NYAKANGO GLOVINE MOTOR BAZAARS LTD P.O BOX 27846 NAKURU Tel:0710472800 EMAIL:glovinemotors@GMAIL.COM CHARLES TOMBE C/O TOMBE & CO. ADVOCATES P.O BOX 16702-20100 NAKURU TELL:0718752316

EMAIL:tombeadvocates@gmail.com

# TOMBE& CO.

Charles Tombe BSc. LL.B

OUR REF:

YOUR REF: TBA

DATE: 9th March, 2024

TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN,

Dear Sir/ Madam,

REF: RECOMMENDATION LETTER FOR LILIAN KERUBO MOTOKI

I CHARLES TOMBE an Advocate of the High Court of Kenya do highly recommend LILIAN KERUBO MOTOKI for employment in the position of an Office Administrator...

I have interacted with her both in her professional capacity being my staff and at personal level. Ms. Lilian Kerubo Motoki is hard working, diligent and efficient in her work with vast experience in Administration and matters relating to the legal field.

Ms. Lilian Kerubo Motoki possesses good communication skills and Leadership skills. She possesses good drafting and Typing skills. She is reliable and effeicient. I wish to state further that, for the 3 years and over that I have known Ms. Lilian Kerubo Motoki, she has proven herself to be self driven, honest and a team player in her dealings.

I thus recommend her without reservations for the job position.

Yours Faithfully,

CHARLES TOMBE- Advocate

### MBOGA G.G. & COMPANY ADVOCATES

& COMMISSIONER FOR OATHS

HEAD OFFICE

Nacha Plaza 3rd Floor, Room 16 Kijabe Row

Email: ggmboga@gmail.com

P.O. BOX 16418-20100 Tel: 051-2210260

NAKURU

Mobile:0725-700248

**BRANCH OFFICE** 

Jostas Building 2<sup>nd</sup> Floor, Room C. 3 Moi Road, Opp. Kenvash Hotel **NAIVASHA** 

GEORGE G. MBOGA LLB (HONS) NRB DIP. IN LAW (KSL)

OUR REF:

YOUR REF:

DATE:10/3/2021

To whom it may concern,

#### RE: LILIAN KERUBO MOTOKI

I have known Lilian Kerubo Motoki for a long time and do truthfully state that she is an intelligent, trustworthy, diligent, and honest young lady. She has been my employee for the past three years and each time she has proven to be reliable in giving positive results in anything that she is called upon to do. She is always enthusiastic about research, her duties and ready to welcome and learn new ideas and concepts. She is committed to her work and she is a good time keeper. Her caring nature and personality allow her to work well in a team, as she always respects the opinions of others.

She is a respectable lady and I do highly recommend her for any job offered by the institution. For any inquiries feel free to contact me via email ggmboga@gmail.com.

GEORGE GISORE MBQG&COMMISSION 16418-20100